<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Eddie Codes</title>
    <link>https://medenfield.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Eddie Codes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>michaeledenfield@gmail.com (Eddie Edenfield)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>michaeledenfield@gmail.com (Eddie Edenfield)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 15:31:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://medenfield.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building transactional email workflows with Drupal and Mandrill</title>
      <link>https://medenfield.github.io/post/building-transaction-email-workflows-drupal-mandrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 15:31:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>michaeledenfield@gmail.com (Eddie Edenfield)</author>
      <guid>https://medenfield.github.io/post/building-transaction-email-workflows-drupal-mandrill/</guid>
      <description>At Open Angler, transactional texts and emails are an important part of how we facilitate and improve upon the process of booking a charter boat or fishing trip online. We use Mandrill to manage our entire suite of outbound email to customers and charter providers, gaining insight into bounce and open confirmation, and empowering our content team to make trivial changes to email templates without developer intervention.
Most web application frameworks have built in or readily available modules to handle sending email, but plaintext is likely the default, and it&amp;rsquo;s likely done from the same server you host your website without any tools for greater insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Drupal 7 platform with Slack</title>
      <link>https://medenfield.github.io/post/drupal-7-slack-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 21:59:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>michaeledenfield@gmail.com (Eddie Edenfield)</author>
      <guid>https://medenfield.github.io/post/drupal-7-slack-integration/</guid>
      <description>At Open Angler, we need to know when booking requests happen on our site. In the old days, a site manager might log in to a dashboard periodically, or perhaps get an email based on a customer action. These days, a push notification is probably better if time is of the essence.
We love Slack, and decided the easiest way to achieve our goal would be to just set up a simple bot that posts to a dedicated channel whenever a new booking request is created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello world</title>
      <link>https://medenfield.github.io/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 13:18:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>michaeledenfield@gmail.com (Eddie Edenfield)</author>
      <guid>https://medenfield.github.io/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
This is my a personal project and portfolio site where I intend to write about new things I&amp;rsquo;m learning about programming and code. I will also revisit things I&amp;rsquo;ve created that I&amp;rsquo;m proud about and want to display publicly. Much of what is contained will be about challenging myself to accomplish X using something new, and then writing about it.
For this site, I went with Hugo - a static site generator written in Go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>